I sent it to an insured.
Yeah bro I think it got bad but too right?
Connect to that idea.
It all started when I had the brilliant idea of arriving in a Cida city.
Only with R$1 ha ha ha.
And guess uncle set up 1 deal in 30 days.
I must.
You're crazy, aren't you?
Well yes I had been buying 2 paçoquinhas there at the Center and I almost made
100 tale mano I sold water on the signal or at least I tried man I got a dog I
sold jujubairo I was kidnapped by a miner and I even stepped on shit I started
doing deliveries I thought of a business strategy and I had to have 7 coffees
and I went crazy but believe it OR not I managed to rent 1 Chevette.
And here in locks and ravines.
This is me.
I'm already on the 20th day of this series watching
by over thirty million people.
You can only be crazy,
right?
I also don't know where this is going.
The car is broken down and I'm here trying to
figure out how to continue all of this.
After all,
there are now only ten days to go.
But please bro if you have any tips let me know there.
What would you do if you had it in my place?
Tamo together.
Oh baby I'm tired of Talking.
That is too much.
Record your food and let's start walking.